tokyowebdesigns.com 2011-11-03

# Tokyo Web Designs - Privacy | English-Japanese Webpage Developers | Japan

### Privacy

By visiting the TokyoWebDesigns.com website (the "Site") you are agreeing with and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy you should immediately cease using the Site.

### Information we collect

#### Information you give us

We receive and store information that you actively provide to us. This may represent a potentially wide range of information. It will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list unless you have specifically opted into a mailing list. We will not use your e-mail address for any other purpose and will not disclose it, without your consent.

#### Information we collect from you

We may from time to time receive and store certain information relating to your use of, and behavior on the Site. This information is commonly referred to as "click stream" information. For example, we may record information such as the areas of the Site you have accessed, the time, date and URL of the pages requested by you, your IP address and your browser software. The recording of such information enables us to monitor the areas of the Site that are most popular and to improve sections of the Site accordingly.

#### Information obtained from "cookies"

The Site may make use of a feature of Internet web browsers called "cookies", which are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are used to maintain session information between your browser and our website, and are required for our website to operate.

### Use and disclosure of your information

We are committed to the protection of your privacy and your personal information. All preliminary project discussions will be treated with the strictest confidence. We will do our utmost to comply with laws relating to privacy, data collection and the use of information that are currently enacted or may be enacted in the future.

To facilitate our efficient use of your information, and to provide you with the services or products requested by you, it may sometimes be necessary for us to disclose your information to third parties. However, this disclosure will only occur in the following circumstances:

#### Our employees, contractors and agents.

From time to time we may engage or employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include, but are not limited to, processing credit card payments, fulfilling orders and delivering products, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and/or providing information technology and related services. Such parties will have access to only that personal information required by them to perform their functions, and may not use such information for any other purposes, nor are they to provide your information to third parties without your consent.

#### Where required by law

In certain circumstances we may be required by law to disclose your personal information. For example, where disclosure is ordered by a Court, or subpoenaed in relation to third party litigation.

### Is my information secure?

We will take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information that we hold about you. Unfortunately though, no server on the Internet, nor any data transmission over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorized access to such information.

### Third party links

The Site may contain links to other sites. With the exception of other sites operated by us, we do not control the information collection of sites reached through links from this Site. If you have any questions about the information collection policies of those sites then you should contact the companies controlling those sites directly.

### Further queries

If we become aware of any ongoing concerns or problems with the Site, we will take the issue seriously and work to address your concerns. If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy, or have a problem or complaint, then you should contact us via our contact page.
